

ABOUT ME

Gender: Male
Birth Place: El Salvador
github.com/mariozelaya23

CONTACT



2286 Goddard Ave Simi Valley CA 93063



310-709-6573



mariozelaya23@gmail.com

INTERESTS

Web Development Programming

Android and IOS Dev Databases

System Administrator Business Analysis

HOBBIES









LANGUAGES

English and Spanish

Mario Zelaya

SYSTEM ADMIN

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I'm a Computer Science Engineer, I have experience in Home and Business Technical Support, Computer repair (PC Hardware), Network Administration, Routers and Switches configurations, Windows Server Administration including Active Directory and Exchange. I have also experienced working with Software Development using C # and ASP.NET and Designing and Writing Databases Structures, Queries, and Stored Procedures.

TECHNICAL

- MS Exchange 2010

WAN, DNS, DHCP, etc.

- Customer Service

operating systems

Programming

Configuring)

PROFICIENCIES:

- Proficiency in Microsoft Office

- Windows Server 2003/2008/2012

- Support and Administration of Active

- PC Hardware Experience (Installing and

- Network administration LAN, WLAN,

- Technical background with Linux

- Knowledge of C# and ASP.Net

- SQL - T-SQL Stored Procedures

EDUCATION

BACHELOR DEGREE

Bachelor in Computer Science Universidad Evangélica de El Salvador

DIPLOMA

Computer Science Engineer

ACHIEVEMENT

Thesis delivered in record time application made in Visual Basic -SQL Server, Android and ASP .net

EXPERIENCE

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

April 2020 to Present | Geeks on Site

- Los Angeles, CA
- •In-Home and Business Technical Support
- •In-Home: Computer Repair (Desktop and Laptops), Network Configuration, Routers Configuration, Data Recovery, and training.
- Business: Server Installation, Backups, Router, and Firewall Configuration.

WEB DEVELOPER

May 2018 to April 2020 | Hosting of El Salvador

- San Salvador, El Salvador

I have helped the rapid growth of company, developing very good quality web pages quickly and supporting in digital marketing, which helped increase sales in the company by 25%.

- Managing complete projects from conception to development including web design, branding, and social media, including any troubleshooting to keep client deliverables on strict deadlines.
- Technologies: WordPress, PHP, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Google AdWords and Analytics, Excel.

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

January 2014 to May 2018 | Soluciones Eficaces

- San Salvador, El Salvador

<u>I have helped the company to implement new technologies, as well as in the improvements in internal processes, which helped the company grow.</u>

- Implement the Server Application (Windows Server) with the collections system (PHP MySQL).
- Implement and Administration of the VOIP Elastix PBX with GSM Gateway.
- Implement, Configure and Administration of the Microsoft Exchange Server and Active Directory.
- Implement and Administration of SQL Server 2014 with Windows Server 2012.
- Generate reports for stakeholders such as monthly results, monthly projections, agent KPI.
- Technologies: VMware, Excel (Pivot Tables, VLOOKUP), SQL Queries, Integration Services, Windows Server and SQL Server, Elastix, Softphone, Active Directory, Exchange, Routers, Switches, GSM.

SOFTWARE QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

January 2013 to January 2014 | Telekenex Telecommunications LLC

San Salvador, El Salvador

I was in charge of the creation and management of the QA department, so, the company greatly improved its communications software.

- Design, construct and implement different types of Test Cases, such as Smoke Testing, Manual Testing, Automated Testing, Regression Testing, and Black Box.
- Technologies: Excel (Testcases), Windows Server, VMWare, Test Complete (automated Testing).